## MUSKILGNANAVATHY P

9843950793



Senior Client Partner

muskilpaulmani@gmail.com



18,Anbu Nagar Main Road Alwarthirunagar Valasaravakkam Chennai 600087.



### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Continuously Evolving Challenging Accounts Receivable or Accounts Payable Position and Customer Support Services with Over 5 Years of Experience. Diverse Analytical Background that includes, Responsible for Calling Insurance Companies and Setting in Motion Follow-up actions on Outstanding Accounts Receivable. Have the Knowledge and Understanding in Denial Management in US Healthcare, Revenue Cycle Management in Medical Billing and Customer Queries.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### Sethu Institute of Technology

BE - CSE (2014-2018)

80%

## Holy Family Girl's Higher Secondary School

2013-2014

87%

#### SKILLS

- Ability to learn New idea of innovation and New Technologies
- Strong Planning Skills to Customer Support Management
- · Leadership Quality and Logical Thinking.
- · Loyal to what I am doing

#### CERTIFICATIONS

- Undergone training on "Red hat Linux system Administration" at WINWAYS.
- Undergone training on "Networking in MNC" at MACNUS SOLUTIONS.
- Undergone an Inplant traning on "Android App Development" at UNIQ TECHNOLOGY.
- Undergone International Hands on Ethical Hacking Workshop at WIKITECHY and MICROSOFT RESEARCH COMMUNITY GROUP.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

# ACCESS HEALTHCARE SERVICES PVT LTD (SEPTEMBER 2019 – AUGUST 2023)

Role: SENIOR CLIENT PARTNER (International Voice Process)

- Call Insurance companies on behalf of physicians and carry out a further examination on outstanding
- Accounts Receivable.
- Prioritize unpaid claims for calling according to the length of time it has been outstanding.
- · Check the relevance of insurance information offered by the patient.
- · Evaluate unpaid insurance claims.
- Call insurance companies and check on the status of the Outstanding claims.
- Transfer the outstanding balance to the patient if he/she doesn't have adequate insurance coverage.
- If the claim has already been paid, ask the insurance company for Explanation of Benefits (EOB).
- · Receive Payment information, if the claims have been processed.
- · Analyze claims in case of any rejections.
- Make corrections to the claim based on inputs from the insurance company and Review the claim allocated and check status by calling the payer.
- · To Ensure deliverables adhere to quality standards.

# ZEALOUS SERVICE PVT LTD (MAY 2018- JUNE 2019)

Role: CUSTOMER SUPPORT EXECUTIVE (International Semi-Voice Process)

- $\scriptstyle \square$  To Handle Customer Queries and Troubleshoot their Problem via E-mail and Chart.
- □ Proficiency in Problem Solving.
- п Perform Date Processing and Database Work.
- □ Interaction with Customer and Solve their Problem.
- □ Answering Customer Calls and Resolving their Issues.

#### **PROJECTS**

Presented a Main Project on " Mobile Application for Dengue Affected Area via GPS.

#### **ACHIEUEMENTS & AWARDS**

- Best Performer in the Month of June 2022 at Access Healthcare.
- High Productivity Employee in the Month of August 2023 at Access Healthcare.

#### **PERSONAL PROFILE:**

Date of Birth: 05.06.1997 Languages: Tamil, English. Material Status: Married.

Hoppies: Using Social Media and Listening Music.

Address: 19, Anbu Nagar Main Road, Alwarthirunagar,

Valasaravakkam, Chennai -600087.

#### **DECLARATION**

I hereby declare that the Information Furnished above are true to the Best of my Knowledge.

Place: Chennai

Date:

P.MUSKILGNANAVATHY